<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Link of SeisPider</title>
    <link>http://link.seispider.top/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Link of SeisPider</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 00:57:40 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://link.seispider.top/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Environmental software construction</title>
      <link>http://link.seispider.top/2018-11-17-work-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 00:57:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://link.seispider.top/2018-11-17-work-environment/</guid>
      <description> Compiler  gfortran for mac
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General geophysics forward modelling codes</title>
      <link>http://link.seispider.top/2018-11-04-general-geophysics-forward-modelling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:57:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://link.seispider.top/2018-11-04-general-geophysics-forward-modelling/</guid>
      <description>Volcano  PF3D: PF3D is a Python module that facilitates volcanic ash dispersal modelling using the FALL3D package
  Geodynamic  ASPECT: A parallel, extensible finite element code to simulate convection in both 2D and 3D models.
 PyLith: an open-source finite-element code for dynamic and quasistatic simulations of crustal deformation, primarily earthquakes and volcanoes.
 Rayleigh: a 3-D convection code designed for the study of dynamo behavior in spherical geometry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seismological forward modelling codes</title>
      <link>http://link.seispider.top/2018-08-02-forward-modelling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:57:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://link.seispider.top/2018-08-02-forward-modelling/</guid>
      <description>Spectrum element method  SES3D: SES3D is a program package for the simulation of elastic wave propagation and waveform inversion in a spherical section. The package is based on a spectral-element discretisation of the seismic wave equation combined with adjoint techniques.
  Reflectivity method  fk: Frequency-Wavenumber (FK) synthetic seismogram package
 telewavesim: Teleseismic body wave simulation with propagation matrix method
  Modal summation  CPS330: General computer program in seismology</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seismological inversion codes</title>
      <link>http://link.seispider.top/2018-08-02-inversion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:57:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://link.seispider.top/2018-08-02-inversion/</guid>
      <description>Structure Full Waveform  lasif: a data-driven end-to-end workflow tool to perform adjoint full seismic waveform inversions.
 SeisFlow: differs from previous open-source software in emphasizing both flexibility and HPC portability.
 DSM kernel: calculate 3D finite frequency Fréchet sensitivity kernels (or 3D waveform partial derivatives) for 1D reference Earth models using Direct Solution Method.
  Surface wave  topo_sp_cu: ray theoretic surface wave tomography code.
 FMTOMO: The forward problem of traveltime prediction is solved using a multi-stage fast marching method (FMM), which is a sophisticated grid-based eikonal solver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seismological data processing codes</title>
      <link>http://link.seispider.top/2018-07-28-data-processing-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 00:57:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://link.seispider.top/2018-07-28-data-processing-code/</guid>
      <description>Retrieve seismology waveforms  Running the scripts and examples - Web Service Fetch scripts - IRIS SeisCode
 SOD - Demo
 IRIS-WS:A Java API that allows direct access to data and information at the DMC from within your programs.
  Data processing Ambient noise  New Codes for Ambient Seismic Noise Analysis
 seissuite 0.1.3 : Python Package Index
 MSNoise | A Python Package for Monitoring Seismic Velocity Changes using Ambient Seismic Noise</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seismology Data</title>
      <link>http://link.seispider.top/2018-07-28-seismology-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 00:57:40 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://link.seispider.top/2018-07-28-seismology-data/</guid>
      <description>Seismic waveforms  FDSN
 Earthquake Center
 国家测震台网地震波形数据管理与共享平台
 IRIS DMC Google Map Service Usage
 International Seismological Centre
 WebDC3 at eida.gfz-potsdam.de
 EarthScope USArray Data Management Short Course
 MUSTANG: Browser station info. (PDF, continuity and so on) which can be obtained from IRIS
  seismic phase peaking tools  PhaseLink: A deep learning approach to seismic phase association
 PSPicker: a matlab tool for automatic phase picking and event location</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>